// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "When was Nepal Rastra Bank established?",
    answer: "B.S. 2013 Baishakh 14",
    options: [
      "B.S. 2013 Baishakh 10",
      "B.S. 2013 Baishakh 14",
      "B.S. 2013 Baishakh 16",
      "B.S. 2013 Baishakh 12" 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "how many Paper Note have been in circulation in Nepal till now?",
    answer: "11",
    options: [
      "12",
      "11",
      "10",
      "8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is the first Joint Venture commercial bank of Nepal?",
    answer: "Nabil Bank",
    options: [
		"Nabil Bank",
      "Everest Bank",
           "SBI Bank",
      "NMB Bank"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many commercial banks are present in Nepal?",
    answer: "27",
    options: [
      "28",
      "27",
      "26",
      "25"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which is the First commercial bank established in Nepal?",
    answer: "Nepal Bank Limited",
    options: [
      "NABIL Bank",
      "Rastriya Banijya Bank",
      "Nepal Rastra Bank",
      "Nepal Bank Limited"


    ]
  },
  
    {
     numb: 6,
   question: "When was Nepal Bank Limited established?",
  answer: "B.S 1994 Kartik 30",
   options: [
   "B.S 1994 Kartik 30",
  "B.S 1994 Kartik 10",
  "B.S 1994 Ashwin 30",
  "B.S 1994 Ashwin 10"
 
   ]
  },
{
     numb: 7,
   question: "Which bank first introduced ATM in Nepal?",
  answer: "Himalayan Bank",
   options: [
   "SBI Bank",
  "Standard Chartered Bank",
  "Himalayan Bank",
  "Nabil Bank"
   ]
  },
{
     numb: 8,
   question: "Your Question is Here",
  answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
   options: [
   "Option 1",
  "option 2",
  "option 3",
  "option 4"
   ]
  },
{
     numb: 9,
   question: "Your Question is Here",
  answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
   options: [
   "Option 1",
  "option 2",
  "option 3",
  "option 4"
   ]
  },
{
     numb: 10,
   question: "Your Question is Here",
  answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
   options: [
   "Option 1",
  "option 2",
  "option 3",
  "option 4"
   ]
  },
];